I guess when I was young I had many
aspirations my name is Daniel here you
can call me him
I'm the CEO of Prudential Insurance
Malaysia Berhad however looking back now
I suppose I always felt that I want to
do something challenging and that is to
be in actually all the time I realized
that it probably does not matter to
greatly what you choose to do so long as
you have the passion to achieve
excellence in whatever you do it is
always important that if it's a job
worth doing it's a job worth doing well
what I love about being a CEO is I get
to be involved in almost all aspects of
the business and at the same time I need
to ensure the correct strategic
direction of the organization with
Prudential a graduate aspire 2018
[Music]